This is gonna be live, man.
My custom burger, the Bullet Head's burger.
Pepper Jack cheese, bacon, sauteed jalapenos,
barbecue sauce, a secret in-house sauce
that Chef put on there.
Chef Romo's about to bring this out right now, man.
You ready for this?
Let's go, let's get a little closer for this.
Talk to me, I'll talk back.
Ooh-wee, burger’s seasoned too,
I don't wanna hear nothing, it's bland.
And it's gonna come looking like this.
I don't wanna hear mine didn't look like that.
The Bullet Head burger, man.
Should I go in?
You ready?
Yeah, let's do it.
Let's go in, see what Chef's doing.
Mm, mm, mm, mm.
I didn't even add the lettuce in the pickles.
Yeah, the jalapenos complement the meat.
Everything goes great together,
especially with the Pepper Jack cheese.
You're getting everything you need
with this burger right here.
I think the Bullet Head burger
is probably the best burger in Las Vegas.
It's got my name on it.
You gotta come correct.
Shout out to Chef Romo.
Thank you for letting this come alive.
The Bullet Head burger will be available all August.
You ain't gonna go wrong with this burger.
Seasoned up bacon, jalapenos, Pepper Jack cheese,
secret sauce, barbecue sauce, phenomenal burger.
Man, it's too easy, bro.
Come see us at Tuscan Cove.
We got you.
Easy.
[Music]